[Kim Seonghyuk as Kwon Hyukjae]
[Jung Myeongcheol as Yoo Sehyun]
[Jung Hyunwoong as Kim Minho]
[Kim Hyeonseo as Sung Ho]
[Sin and Love]
[Episode 9]
Yoo Sehyun,
you're under arrest on suspicion of
illegal drug dealing at Gangnam Palace.
Please come with me.
Who authorized this?
Someone reported you
for illegal drug dealing.
Who reported it?
It was an anonymous tip.
We've secured the evidence.
I didn't do it!
This case is under investigation.
What you're doing constitutes
obstruction of justice.
I didn't do it.
Please come with me.
Sehyun.
You'll be fine.
Go with him.
Let's go.
[Officer Kwon Hyukjae: Sung Ho, the
drug dealing suspicion against Yoo Sehyun]
[has been confirmed, huh?]
I've been assigned to interrogate you.
Do you have
anything to confess?
You feel like a stranger.
What do you mean?
We were together a second ago,
and now you want me to confess?
That was then; this is now.
I missed you.
We've only been apart for an hour.
Even so,
this hour has been hell for me.
Let's not talk about personal matters.
Then come closer.
I'll tell you the truth.
Now's not the time for that.
Why?
Isn't this what you want?
The door's locked
and the camera's off.
Isn't this what you want?
You're a suspect,
and I'm a cop.
So?
You don't want to do it?
You're playing with fire.
I know.
If you really are a drug dealer,
listening to you makes me an accomplice.
You know it's not me.
But they don't believe you.
It's Kwon Hyukjae.
Do you have proof?
All the evidence points to you.
At Gangnam Palace, you were his sidekick.
Do you know about
the trading locations and such?
I need details.
No, nothing.
I was in charge of accounting
at Gangnam Palace,
but I don't know who he dealed with.
And every time he made a call,
he'd avoid me.
Even during transactions,
I was just on the sidelines.
Sung Ho.
That's why I need you.
Please help me.
How can I help?
Before that...
I really want to kiss you.
Sung Ho!
Wait.
Leave everything to me.
Now, you'll
begin your confession.
We're doing this again?
Fine, let's do this.
How did Kwon Hyukjae communicate?
Let's start with his phone number.
I don't know how he communicated,
but he used a different number
every time he called.
What about the transactions?
Cash or bank transfers?
Account numbers?
I don't know anything.
Because he never told me anything.
I was only in charge
of the palace's accounting.
The incoming money
were all laundered.
Then...
do you know
where the transactions took place?
I don't, but...
Assemblyman Jo...
He mentioned Assemblyman Jo once.
Assemblyman Jo?
The Assemblyman Jo I know?
That's right,
the presidential candidate Jo Kanghoon.
Kwon Hyukjae once said
that Assemblyman Jo is the real boss,
and he's just
working under him.
Then...
can you testify to that?
Me?
Of course not.
I have no proof.
I didn't record him saying that.
If I create an opportunity for you,
can you record it?
I'm afraid not.
Kwon Hyukjae wouldn't
say things like that to me.
He only mentioned Assemblyman Jo
when he was drunk.
Right.
So I'll create an opportunity for you.
How?
I'll get you out first.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
You take charge of Yoo Sehyun's case.
Yes, sir.
Did Sung Ho tell you to
look out for Yoo Sehyun?
Not yet.
He'll come to you for Yoo Sehyun.
When he does,
report to me ASAP.
What if Sung Ho...
finds evidence against you?
Let him find it.
But only what I deliberately prepared.
You've got
everything planned out, huh?
If I couldn't handle things like this,
I wouldn't be where I am now.
Go check out Yoo Sehyun.
We need him alive.
Yes, sir.
Yoo Sehyun,
you have a visitor.
Sehyun, it's me.
Why are you here?
To see how you're doing.
I bought you what you like.
After doing this to me,
what's the use of anything else?
Yes, I did this to you,
and all the evidence points to you.
What?
Sehyun, what I want is Sung Ho.
I want him to stop looking into
this case.
That's what I've been waiting for.
Find someone else.
I can't help you.
How many times must I tell you
you don't have a choice?
Either you do as I say,
or you can keep rotting in here.
It's up to you.
What's in it for me?
Sung Ho?
Sung Ho.
Stop looking into
Yoo Sehyun's case.
It won't do you any good.
Seriously?
After you made the arrest?
It's an order.
An order?
Whose order?
Kwon Hyukjae's?
What did you say when you shot him?
You said you didn't want to
be his dog anymore.
So what's this now?
You're being his lackey again.
You don't understand...
I do.
You're working for him.
I'm scared too.
But...
Fear is no excuse for compromise.
Give me...
a bit more time.
Time won't wait for you.
You have to fight for it.
Did you get some sleep?
Not really.
I've been thinking about how to save you.
Did you
figure something out?
No.
I'm so worried.
You look worse than yesterday.
Sung Ho,
it's okay.
We could just give up.
You are
more shaken than yesterday.
It's all because of you.
Sung Ho.
If I can't get out,
will you wait for me?
Yeah.
Whether it's 10 or 20 years,
I'll wait for you.
Don't wait for me.
If I can't get out,
I want you to find someone else
and live a happy life.
No.
You're the only one for me.
I promise I'll get you out.
No matter what happens...
I will make you happy.
No matter what...
I'll find a way to get you out.
I'll save you.
Got it?
[Sin and Love]